HAOYUE ZHOU

Address: 1000 Duke St, #18 NC 27701(willing to relocate) Contact No.: 919.995.1916 | E-mail: hz67@duke.edu

Qualifications Profile

Exceptionally be skilled, highly organized, and solutions-oriented professional, with knowledge in business analysis, research and excellent presentation. Known for reliability and dedication; be able to take on challenges, manage diverse and increasing responsibilities, and accomplish simple-to-complex goals while maintaining composure even under high-pressure and challenging environments. Accustomed to interacting and collaborating with all levels of individuals including customers, upper management, and staff. Equipped with articulate written and verbal communication skills; bilingual in English and Chinese. Over 6 years experiences with MS Office, and technically be proficient with SQL, C#, Visual Studio, MATLAB, Java and MS Project.

Education

Master of Management • Dec. 2013 DUKE UNIVERSITY, DURHAM, NC USA GPA: 3.5/4.0

Bachelor of Science in Electrical and Computer Engineering • May 2012

NEW YORK INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, NEW YORK, USA

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical and Computer Engineering • June 2012

Nanjing University of Posts and Telecommunications

Work Experience

KIT SOLUTIONS | PITTSBURG, PA, USA

Marketing & Management Intern• June 2013-August 2013

- Conducted primary and secondary market research for the company, and monitored internal database to maintain competitive intelligence and support management decision
- Researched and provided the most suitable CRM system to improve customer retention rate and to seek potential customers
- Managed the CRM system and proposed a preliminary roadmap for the company's market entry in China
- Assisted CEO in arranging academic exchange activities for clients in China and pursued future business opportunities
- Assisted Data Department and applied Visual Studio & SQL to check the annual customer report for the government of South Carolina

LENOVO | RALEIGH, NC, USA

Marketing Researcher • Jan. 2013-May 2013

- Conducted a thorough market research to assess the profitability of insourcing a data center in North America
- Performed cost-benefit analysis, partnership and competitive analysis, and financial analysis
- Directed and guided a team of six people in accurately evaluating alternative plans for Lenovo's breakout growth in the Data Center Market
- Conducted primary and secondary research on 3' Cs & 4' Ps and presented to senior manager and related technology department

NEW YORK INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, NEW YORK, NY, USA

Product Design & Development Researcher • Sep. 2011-May 2012

- Led four undergraduate-level students in designing a central gravity detection device to detect the central gravity change of Parkinson patients
- Conducted weekly presentation of effective development and recommendations to the supervisor of the project
- Displayed various trial experiments to gather effective data and applied MATLAB for further data analysis
- Took a role in leadership to manage project timeline and to ensure effective outcomes

ZHENJIANG XIN DA ENGINEERING CO., LTD, CHINA

Project Management Intern • July 2011-Aug 2011

- Interviewed with suppliers, contractors, and government officials to improve cooperation among different organizations
- Led a team to collaborated with other teams to execute senior management's plan
- Proposed and presented constructing plan to upper management resulting in positive feedback

Personal Interests

HIIT Training, reading, hiking, poor travel, cooking, Taekwondo and music